Finding Aid for the Brainard Bartwell Cheney and Frances Neel Cheney Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Brainard Bartwell Cheney and Frances Neel Cheney Papers File Listing
  - Subject Files
    - Bibliographies and Lists—McGregor Library Reading List in American History, March 1950 (Box 84, File 6)
    - Bibliographies and Lists—Scholarships, Fellowships and Loans News Service, January 1956 and 1958 (Box 84, File 7)
    - Bibliographies and Lists—38 Cards with Reference Book Bibliographic Information (Box 84, File 8)
    - Communism, Japan and Other (International Union of Students) (Box 84, File 9)
    - Eakins Press (Box 84, File 10)
    - Gordon, Caroline (Mostly Reviews) (Box 84, File 11)
    - Japan, Japanese Art (Box 84, File 12)
    - Japan, Japanese Art and Art I n Japan (Box 84, File 13)
    - Japan, Bibliographic Materials (Box 85, File 1)
    - Japan, Bookstores and 2nd Hand Dealers, etc. (Box 85, File 2)
    - Japan, Cheney’s Impressions, etc. (Box 85, File 3)
    - Japan, Clippings (Box 85, File 4)
    - Japan, Clippings (Box 85, File 5)
    - Japan, Copyright (Box 85, File 6)
    - Japan, Dance (Box 85, File 7)
    - Japan, Education, General (American Occupation) (Box 85, File 8)
    - Japan, G. I. Babies (Box 85, File 9)
    - Japan, Government Publications (Box 85, File 10)
    - Japan, Kokusai Bunka Shinkokai (The Society for International Cultural Relations) (Box 85, File 11)
    - Japan, Libraries (Box 85, File 12)
    - Japan, Music (Box 85, File 13)
    - Japan, Novels (Box 85, File 14)
    - Japan, Reading Interests (Box 85, File 15)
    - Japan, Theatre (Kabuki, Bunraku, Noh, etc.) (Box 85, File 16)
    - Japan, Theatre (Kabuki, Bunraku, Noh, etc.) (Box 86, File 1)
    - Japan, Tourists (Box 86, File 2)
    - Japan, Travel (Box 86, File 3)
    - Japan, Travel (Box 86, File 4)
    - Japan, Women (Box 86, File 5)
    - Japan, World Government (Le Compas International and Clippings) (Box 86, File 6)
    - Library Publications, 1947-1951 (Box 86, File 7)
    - Library Publications, 1953-1954 (Box 86, File 8)
    - Library Publications, 1955 (Box 86, File 9)
    - Library Publications, 1957 (Box 87, File 1)
    - Library Publications, 1957 (Box 87, File 2)
    - Library Publications, 1958-1959, 1961 (Box 87, File 3)
    - Materials of Personal Interest, Print of the Artful Dodger and a Union pamphlet (Box 87, File 4)
    - Printed Programs (Box 87, File 5)
    - Publication Announcements (Box 87, File 6)
    - Queens College Conference on Access to Knowledge and Information in the Social Sciences and Humanities (Box 87, File 7)
    - Queens College Conference on Access to Knowledge and Information in the Social Sciences and Humanities (Box 87, File 8)
    - Queens College Conference on Access to Knowledge and Information in the Social Sciences and Humanities (Box 87, File 9)
    - Rugby Restoration Association (Box 87, File 10)
    - Tennessee Newspapers, Rates and Data, 1953 (Box 87, File 11)
  - Library Writings by Other Authors
    - Articles and Essays--Betts, Emmett Albert-Reading Abilities: Averages and Deviations. Education 74: 323, January 1954 No 5 Vance, Earl L.- Periodical Reading Courses: Their Place and Function in American Education,Education 74:81, October 1953 No 2 (Box 87, File 12)
    - Articles and Essays--Bowen, Jean and Paul T. Jackson A Study of Periodicals Indexed in Notes’ Index of Record Reviews, Notes Winter 1965/66 (Box 87, File 13)
    - Speeches-- Robb, Felix Untitled Speech- Chicago Meeting of the American Library Association, February 1948 (Box 87, File 14)
  - Personal and Biographical Materials
    - Assorted (Box 87, File 15)
    - Beta Phi Mu Award, Certificate (Box 87, File 16)
    - Beta Phi Mu Award, Correspondence (Box 87, File 17)
    - Beta Phi Mu Award, Publications (Box 88, File 1)
    - Beta Phi Mu Award (Box 88, File 2)
    - Biographical Data (Box 88, File 3)
    - Biographical Index Questionnaires (Who’s Who, Foremost Women in Communication, Etc.) (Box 88, File 4)
    - Clippings (Box 88, File 5)
    - Clippings (Box 88, File 6)
    - Employment Information for year in Japan (Box 88, File 7)
    - Isadore Gilbert Mudge Citation (Box 88, File 8)
    - Personal Data Sheet (Box 88, File 9)
    - Printed Biographical Materials (Box 88, File 10)
    - Envelopes (Box 89)
    - Envelopes (Box 90)
    - Envelopes (Box 91)